SATAN SAID : " I AM BETTER THAN HIM .
YOU CREATED ME FROM FIRE AND CREATED HIM FROM CLAY . "
" REPRIEVE ME UNTIL THE DAY THEY ARE RESURRECTED . "
SOUL
Mum .
When can we slaughter another one , mum ?
Why don 't you pick up the charcoals first ?
They 're still hot , mum .
Can I choose which one for today ?
You 're such a ...
Enough . Get Along .
Go check on the trap .
Can we ?
Angah .
Along .
- Keep an eye on your brother . - Alright , mum .
Along , this is enough for a week .
Don 't speak of it .
Let 's go .
Along ! Along ...
Remember what mum said . Keep your head down .
Quick .
Mum !
Wait here .
Angah .
Didn 't I say pick up the charcoals earlier on ?
Child , where are you from ?
What 's your name ?
Little girl , I 'll fetch you some water .
She 's probably from the village across the river .
Got lost in the forest .
- I think ... - She 's probably mute , mum .
Mum , let me clean her up .
Let 's bring her to the village across the river .
Maybe the villagers know her .
What 's up with you ?
Mum .
This noon at the trap
we saw a deer .
Dead . Hung by a tree .
And then ? What did you guys do ?
I wanted to bring the deer home .
- Should last us a week . - Are you crazy ?
It 's already dead , hanging by the tree .
A tiger might be lurking around .
Hey , don 't simply take anything in the jungle .
Listen well .
Never believe everything that you see or hear ...
in the jungle .
- If dad was around , he 'd have ... - And then ?
Is he here right now ?
Anyway , there 's no tiger in this jungle .
There 're only crocodiles and lizards .
Mum , crocodiles and lizards don 't climb trees .
You 're right .
Or could be ...
this is something else .
Something old people always talk about ...
related to deer .
They say ...
It likes to roam around the jungle
with Its ghostly dogs .
Whoever sees It
will fall ill ...
or die .
What 's this " something " , mum ?
It swore a solemn oath to not return home
until It got what It hunted for .
Day and night
It hunted ,
slaying innumerable creatures
especially ...
deers
and children .
It threw away the unfavourable ones .
Until one day ...
the jungle put a spell on It .
So It became a regular denizen of the jungle
or some people called It ...
the ghost hunter .
It eats flesh
and drinks blood .
To this day ,
It 's still hunting .
So , the deer might be ...
When you hear dogs barking ...
or the sound of nightjars
flying in flock at night
you 'll know that It 's nearby .
So when It 's nearby ,
pick up
two stones
knock them while calling out
" Grandpa , bring us their hearts "
Why must we say that , mum ?
You must play Its game ,
asking for what It 's hunted
so that It believes that you 're Its follower .
Mum .
What do the nightjars sound like ?
What ?
So ...
the deer ...
This means It 's nearby ?
It 's simple .
Find two stones and then ...
It 's here .
Mum !
When the moon is full ,
all of you will die .
What do we do now , mum ?
Excuse me .
I was just passing by .
Look .
These stones look strange .
That 's why I stopped by to take a look .
No idea .
They fell down last night .
Where are you from ?
I 'm from the other side of the river .
I come here to collect plants in the swamp .
I hope you don 't mind .
We don 't mind at all .
You should inform your husband too .
There are only three of us .
You can call me Tok .
I hope you won 't mind what I 'm about to tell you .
I know a few things .
Look .
These stones are bad omens .
They often mean bad things will happen soon .
- I think ... - Stay for a while .
Have some coffee
or tea ?
Nevermind .
I have to go .
Next time , maybe .
Why don 't the two of you
go pick these stones
and throw them away ?
Come on . Go .
I have some advice .
If there 's anything amiss
anything
come look for me .
I live on that hill .
Along .
Full moon is due in a couple of days , right ?
Yes . Why ?
Why ?
Didn 't you hear what the little girl said just now ?
That 's nonsense .
Who knows what happened to her when she was lost in the jungle .
I shouldn 't have greeted her that day .
It wasn 't that .
Along .
Last night , I think I saw ...
What happened to that girl wasn 't our fault .
So , keep in mind , don 't mention this to anyone .
Along ?
Mum , where are you going ?
Along is too feverish . I will look for Tok .
Along ?
We live too far to ask for others ' help .
We need to ward off her misfortune .
It might be just a disease but who knows ?
Things like this can 't be taken lightly .
Something evil has entered this area .
Go home and take a look at your daughter .
Take this .
Throw it faraway into the water .
And these doves ,
do as I 've told you .
Understand ?
You don 't have to stay on that hill .
Don 't worry .
I 'm used to it already .
We don 't have guests often .
It 'll be nice to have another adult around as company .
I only have these kids .
What a pain in the neck .
Do you miss Dad ?
Do you think Dad will ever come back ?
I don 't know .
I just hope he 'll come back soon .
Me too .
If Dad was around ,
Mum wouldn 't be as cranky as she is now .
Listen here . I 've some advice to give you .
Hey , it 's okay .
It 's late .
I have to go .
Alright .
When you feel like visiting , just stop by anytime .
Grandpa , bring us their hearts ...
Have you seen a girl ?
About his height .
No , we didn 't .
Are you sure ?
No one came by .
Try looking around in the village across the river .
I came
from there .
There 's no other kid except my children .
Look for her somewhere else !
Mum .
Don 't you think that guy looks like a hunter ?
He even has a spear .
Looks like he just returned from war .
Filthy . Ill-mannered .
Something isn 't right about that stranger .
What do you mean ?
Exactly . Why was he looking for the girl ?
That 's why .
Perhaps the girl was running away from him .
Who knows ?
I was only asking .
He might be her father .
Many strange things happened since the girl 's arrival .
And now ,
this stranger .
Maybe he 's the cause .
We 're now living in a dangerous time .
Many people are desperate
and feel unsafe .
Angah !
Angah ...
Along ?
Along !
What happened to Along ?
Along went missing .
She wasn 't there when we woke up this morning .
I can sense there 's a stranger around here .
- A man ? - Yes .
He stopped by our house yesterday .
Why ?
What did he want ?
He asked whether we 've seen a little girl .
A little girl ?
So have you seen her ?
Along fell ill yesterday
and she went missing today .
I think it 's related to him .
I 'm not sure .
I 'm going there .
I 'll try to look for Along along the way .
Along ?
Where did you go ?
What happened to you ?
I found her in the jungle .
Fool ! Don 't try to fool me ! What 've you done to my daughter ?
- I 'll slit your throat with this machete ! - Ask her yourself !
Where did you get this dagger ?
So it 's true that the little girl was here .
- I told you there was no one here . - Don 't you dare lie to me !
Yes , she was here .
- Along ! - She followed us home .
Mum took her in .
Mum gave her food .
- Along ! - Mister .
Let me take you ...
to where she is .
- Please leave my family alone . - Shut up , Angah !
This boy will take me to her .
After seeing the little girl , I 'll leave this place .
It 's okay , mum .
I 'm here .
Let Angah take him to her .
Along .
Many things had happened .
We didn 't know what to do .
There 's an open field
with a big dead tree in the middle .
She 's there .
Are you sure it wasn 't him ?
Let 's just leave this place .
Where ?
To the village across the river ? It 'll take us a day to get there .
With your condition like this ?
What condition should I be ... before we can leave , mum ?
We must bring the charcoals with us , Along .
You know that too .
We have
nothing .
Tell me , mum .
When was the last time you prostrated and asked for help ?
Are you still expecting for your dead husband to return and help ?
Or ...
are you waiting for me to prostrate for you , fool ?
Why don 't you just die , useless mother !
Tok .
Did you find your sister ?
Be patient , child .
We all belong to Him .
Tok .
There 's something wrong around here .
Something that we can 't see
and it 's evil !
There 's always something evil around us .
You don 't have to be afraid .
The things that you can 't see or hold ...
have no power over you .
It can only hurt you through humans .
The stranger ...
So , remember .
Don 't trust others too much .
Run !
So it 's true that you saw that little girl .
Where is the body ?
We left it at the open field .
Hopefully someone else sees it .
I don 't want my kids to ...
Angah already showed the stranger where the body is .
He was the one who found Along .
- We should help him in return . - Help ?
Did he say where he came from ?
Did he ?
He said from the village across the river .
Do you know what happened in that village ?
What ?
All the houses were burnt down to the ground .
There 's nothing left .
What happened exactly ?
Why did the little girl run away ?
The little girl didn 't run away .
You should already know by now
that she 's not an ordinary child .
So who 's that stranger ?
What should we do ?
Things are getting complicated .
Humans thrive and perish along with nature .
And now , the stranger has the body back .
We can never know what will happen next .
Mum !
Help me .
I need to ask for something .
Angah ?
Have you packed the charcoals ?
Just take what we have .
There 's still a bit more .
Hurry up , we don 't have much time , Angah !
I 'm hungry .
Can we eat first ?
Go now and do as I said !
Angah ?
Angah !
You said you would leave this place .
You found the little girl .
What are you still doing here ?
I 'm here to look for your son .
What do you want from my son ?
Who are you exactly ?
Please don 't get me wrong .
Don 't you dare lie to me .
We don 't have much time .
Things will worsen .
Worsen ?
What 's worse than having my dead daughter 's body in the house
while my son went missing ?
Listen here !
You must believe me if you want to stay safe .
- Or else ... - Or else what ?
Please believe me .
Didn 't I find your lost daughter in the jungle ?
Was it really you who found her ?
Don 't you lie to her !
You must leave this place .
Don 't believe ...
Why don 't you leave this place peacefully ?
This woman !
You should leave now if you want to be safe .
Fine .
I 'll find your son myself .
I think ...
you need this spear more than me .
I don 't understand .
Don 't go . You can 't fight him .
You 'd better wait here .
Believe me .
I must find Angah before he does .
Let me do it instead .
Look after your daughter .
We don 't know what he 's done to the girl 's body .
Better if I kill him .
Wait here .
I 've killed the boy .
You 're willing to sacrifice his life .
Did you take a good look at his face ...
when you killed him ?
Didn 't you pity him ?
He was possessed .
I couldn 't save him .
Same as my daughter .
She 's done her part .
This body is for the next child .
It 's the child 's turn now .
Let me ask you again .
What did you really see ...
when you slit his throat ?
It 's easy to fool humans .
You were given so many signs .
You could 've saved that family .
But all you thought about was your daughter .
You were selfish .
So , why must I prostrate ...
to humans like you ?
" Humans " ?
What do you mean ?
Who are you exactly ?
You don 't need to know who we are .
" We " ?
It was you !
You deceived me with your tricks !
All we need to do is whisper .
And you obeyed our whispers .
You 're more powerful !
You know that we 've no power over you
unless it 's His will .
What else will you do to my daughter ?
This is just a body ...
that will rot and become clay .
Endless revenge !
You 're willing to damn yourself because of clay !
Your time has passed .
Don 't regret the past , for it 's over ...
or be intoxicated with the ephemeral present .
Ephemerality belongs to us .
But the next life ...
will be as eternal ...
as your soul .
Where do you think ...
your soul will go ?
Will your soul ...
rise like fire that reaches the heavens ...
or will your soul fall like ashes ...
that scatter over the ground ?